oximity.com 2016-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Oximity

Oximity Limited (" **Oximity** ", " **Us** " or " **We** ") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. 

This policy (together with our Terms of Use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. 

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the " **Act** "), the data controller is Oximity Limited a company registered in England and Wales with company number 07473604. 

##  Information we may collect from you 

We may collect and process the following data about you: 

  * information that you provide by filling in forms when using or registering to use any Oximity mobile application (the " **App** ") or our website, [www.oximity.com](https://www.oximity.com/) (the " **Website** "), subscribing to our services, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with the App or the Website; 
  * if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence; 
  * we may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them; 
  * details of your use of the App and your visits to the Website including, but not limited to, amounts paid, internet traffic data, location data, blogs and other communication data and the resources that you access; 
  * device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information); and 
  * information about your actual location, like geolocation data of a mobile device. We may also use various technologies to determine location. 

##  IP addresses 

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. 

##  Cookies 

The App and Our Website use cookies to distinguish you from other users of our App and Website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our App and Website and also allows us to improve our App and Website. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie Policy. 

## Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

##  Information Security 

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the App and the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

##  Uses made of the information 

We use information held about you in the following ways: 

  * to ensure that the App and the Website and their content are presented in the most effective manner for you and for your mobile device or computer; 
  * to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes; 
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us; 
  * to analyse the ways in which you use the Website to ensure you get the best experience; 
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so; and 
  * to notify you about changes to our service. 

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users. We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience. 

##  Disclosure of your information 

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties: 

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; 
  * in order to obtain analytics information which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you visit our App and Website and also allows us to improve our App and Website; 
  * if Oximity or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; and 
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](https://www.oximity.com/newsweb/userinfo/termsOfUse.xhtml) and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Oximity, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

The data we disclose to third parties in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside of the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "). 

##  Your rights 

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [personal.data@oximity.com](mailto:personal.data@oximity.com)

Any App or the Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

##  Access to information 

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

##  Changes to our Privacy Policy 

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. 

##  Contact 

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [privacy.policy@oximity.com](mailto:privacy.policy@oximity.com)
